At Tufts, A Weekly Gazette for the University UP151
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
At Tufts, A Weekly Gazette for the University
1976 -- 1979
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Communications
UP151
1.0 Linear Feet
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains issues of At Tufts. Published weekly from April 1976 to December 1979(?), "At Tufts" began as a weekly calendar of events but widened its scope to include news items. From 1976-79 it was known as 'At Tufts: A Weekly Calendar for the University.' Also included is a sample edition of a tabloid publication 'Tufts University Journal & Review,' dated October 4, 1979, which was intended to take the place of 'At Tufts.' It was published by the Office of Public Information.
Missing Issues: Volume 2, 1976-77, Numbers 1,12,14,15,17, 18 (September 10, December 10 and 23 and January 7, 20, and 27): Volume 3, 1977-78, Numbers 2 and 36 (September 16 and May 26): Volume 5, 1979, Number 6 (October 12).
- At Tufts, A Weekly Gazette for the University, 1976 -- 1979; UP151.001; 1.0 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains the publication "At Tufts" which was published weekly from April 1976 to December 1979(?). "At Tufts" began as a weekly calendar of events but widened its scope to include news items. From 1976-79 it was known as 'At Tufts: A Weekly Calendar for the University.' Also included is a sample edition of a tabloid publication 'Tufts University Journal & Review,' dated October 4, 1979, which was intended to take the place of 'At Tufts.'
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - At Tufts, 1976-04-23; UP151.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1976-04-30; UP151.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1976-05-07; UP151.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1976-05-14; UP151.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1976-05-21; UP151.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1976-05-28; UP151.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1976-06-04; UP151.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1976-06-11; UP151.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1976-06-18; UP151.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1976-06-25; UP151.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1976-07-02; UP151.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1976-07-09; UP151.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1976-07-16; UP151.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1976-07-23; UP151.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1976-07-30; UP151.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1976-08-06; UP151.001.001.00016 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1976-09-03; UP151.001.001.00017 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1976-09-17; UP151.001.001.00018 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1976-09-24; UP151.001.001.00019 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1976-10-01; UP151.001.001.00020 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1976-10-08; UP151.001.001.00021 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1976-10-15; UP151.001.001.00022 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1976-10-22; UP151.001.001.00023 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1976-10-29; UP151.001.001.00024 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1976-11-05; UP151.001.001.00025 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1976-11-12; UP151.001.001.00026 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1976-11-19; UP151.001.001.00027 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1976-12-03; UP151.001.001.00028 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1976-12-17; UP151.001.001.00029 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1977-01-13; UP151.001.001.00030 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1976-02-04; UP151.001.001.00031 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1977-02-11; UP151.001.001.00032 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1977-02-18; UP151.001.001.00033 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1977-02-25; UP151.001.001.00034 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1977-03-04; UP151.001.001.00035 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1977-03-11; UP151.001.001.00036 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1977-03-18; UP151.001.001.00037 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1977-03-25; UP151.001.001.00038 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1977-04-01; UP151.001.001.00039 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1977-04-08; UP151.001.001.00040 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1977-04-15; UP151.001.001.00041 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1977-04-29; UP151.001.001.00043 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1977-05-06; UP151.001.001.00044 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1977-05-13; UP151.001.001.00045 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1977-05-20; UP151.001.001.00046 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1977-05-27; UP151.001.001.00047 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1977-06-03; UP151.001.001.00048 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1977-06-10; UP151.001.001.00049 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1977-06-17; UP151.001.001.00050 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1977-06-24; UP151.001.001.00051 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1977-07-01; UP151.001.001.00052 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1977-07-08; UP151.001.001.00053 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1977-07-15; UP151.001.001.00054 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1977-07-22; UP151.001.001.00055 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1977-07-29; UP151.001.001.00056 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1977-09-02; UP151.001.001.00057 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1977-09-09; UP151.001.001.00058 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1977-09-16; UP151.001.001.00059 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1977-09-23; UP151.001.001.00060 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1977-09-30; UP151.001.001.00061 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1977-10-07; UP151.001.001.00062 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1977-10-14; UP151.001.001.00063 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1977-10-21; UP151.001.001.00064 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1977-10-28; UP151.001.001.00065 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1977-10-28; UP151.001.001.00066 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1977-11-04; UP151.001.001.00067 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1977-11-11; UP151.001.001.00068 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1977-11-18; UP151.001.001.00069 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1977-12-02; UP151.001.001.00070 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1977-12-09; UP151.001.001.00071 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1977-12-16; UP151.001.001.00072 (Box 1)
  - At Tufts, 1978-01-06; UP151.001.002.00001 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1978-01-13; UP151.001.002.00002 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1978-01-20; UP151.001.002.00003 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1978-01-27; UP151.001.002.00004 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1978-02-03; UP151.001.002.00005 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1978-02-13; UP151.001.002.00006 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1978-02-17; UP151.001.002.00007 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1978-02-24; UP151.001.002.00008 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1978-03-03; UP151.001.002.00009 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1978-03-10; UP151.001.002.00010 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1978-03-17; UP151.001.002.00011 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1978-03-24; UP151.001.002.00012 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1978-03-30; UP151.001.002.00013 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1978-04-07; UP151.001.002.00014 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1978-04-14; UP151.001.002.00015 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1978-04-21; UP151.001.002.00016 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1978-04-28; UP151.001.002.00017 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1978-05-05; UP151.001.002.00018 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1978-05-12; UP151.001.002.00019 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1978-05-19; UP151.001.002.00020 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1978-05-26; UP151.001.002.00021 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1978-06-02; UP151.001.002.00022 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1978-06-09; UP151.001.002.00023 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1978-06-16; UP151.001.002.00024 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1978-06-23; UP151.001.002.00025 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1978-06-30; UP151.001.002.00026 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1978-07-07; UP151.001.002.00027 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1978-07-14; UP151.001.002.00028 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1978-07-21; UP151.001.002.00029 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1978-07-28; UP151.001.002.00030 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1978-09-01; UP151.001.002.00031 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1978-09-08; UP151.001.002.00032 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1978-09-15; UP151.001.002.00033 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1978-09-22; UP151.001.002.00034 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1978-09-29; UP151.001.002.00035 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1978-10-06; UP151.001.002.00036 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1978-10-13; UP151.001.002.00037 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1978-10-20; UP151.001.002.00038 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1978-10-27; UP151.001.002.00039 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1978-11-03; UP151.001.002.00040 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1978-11-10; UP151.001.002.00041 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1978-11-17; UP151.001.002.00042 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1978-12-01; UP151.001.002.00043 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1978-12-08; UP151.001.002.00044 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1978-12-15; UP151.001.002.00045 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1979-01-12; UP151.001.002.00046 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1979-01-19; UP151.001.002.00047 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1979-01-26; UP151.001.002.00048 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1979-02-02; UP151.001.002.00049 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1979-02-09; UP151.001.002.00050 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1979-02-16; UP151.001.002.00051 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1979-02-23; UP151.001.002.00052 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1979-03-02; UP151.001.002.00053 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1979-03-09; UP151.001.002.00054 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1979-03-16; UP151.001.002.00055 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1979-03-23; UP151.001.002.00056 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1979-03-30; UP151.001.002.00057 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1979-04-06; UP151.001.002.00058 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1979-04-13; UP151.001.002.00059 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1979-04-20; UP151.001.002.00060 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1979-04-27; UP151.001.002.00061 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1979-04-27; UP151.001.002.00062 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1979-05-04; UP151.001.002.00063 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1979-05-11; UP151.001.002.00064 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1979-05-18; UP151.001.002.00065 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1979-05-25; UP151.001.002.00066 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1979-06-02; UP151.001.002.00067 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1979-06-08; UP151.001.002.00068 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1979-06-15; UP151.001.002.00069 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1979-09-07; UP151.001.002.00070 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1979-09-14; UP151.001.002.00071 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1979-09-21; UP151.001.002.00072 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1979-09-28; UP151.001.002.00073 (Box 2)
  - Journal and Review, 1979-10-04; UP151.001.002.00074 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1979-10-05; UP151.001.002.00075 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1979-10-12; UP151.001.002.00076 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1979-10-19; UP151.001.002.00077 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1979-10-26; UP151.001.002.00078 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1979-11-02; UP151.001.002.00079 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1979-11-09; UP151.001.002.00080 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1979-11-16; UP151.001.002.00081 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1979-11-30; UP151.001.002.00082 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1979-12-07; UP151.001.002.00083 (Box 2)
  - At Tufts, 1979-12-14; UP151.001.002.00084 (Box 2)